

VINICIUS PONTAROLLA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I am a junior developer, currently enrolled in a FullStack Software course. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Python. I have three years of experience in Customer Support. I am a valuable team-player with strong communication skills and effective problem solving ability. I am eager to enter the tech industry into an exciting development team where I can grow and contribute.

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Python
- MySQL
- Git and GitHub
- Microsoft Office package
- Adobe package

CONTACT

vinipontarolla@gmail.com +49 176 805 99952 https://github.com/Vepp1 https://www.linkedin.com/in/viniciuspontarolla-826546156/ Beckersgraben 20, - Bad Hersfeld, Germany 36251

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Warehouse employee

Amazon / September 2021 - Currently Bad Hersfeld - Germany

- Stower and Picker.
- Cartrunner and Dock Responsible.

Costumer Support

MadeiraMadeira / November 2019 - October 2020, Curitiba - Brazil

- Online assistance to customers.
- Reverse logistics.
- Schedule pick-up dates.

EDUCATION

Code Institute / Dublin - Ireland (Online)

Full Stack Software Development March 2022 - (ECD) December 2022

- Some of the modules I completed: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Users Experience, Automation.
- Upcoming modules are: jQuery, APIs, Flask, Framework and a specialization in React.

Tecpuc / Curitiba - Brazil - Pontifical Catholic University of Parana

Information Technology (High Scool) February 2015 - November 2018

- HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Adobe Package
- MySql
- Robotics

LANGUAGES

Portuguese - Native speaker English - C1 Italian - C1 German - A2